BRANDON LAMBRECHT

NASHVILLE,TN | 406-281-2139 |BRANDONJLAMBRECHT@GMAIL.COM LinkedIn: BrandonLambrecht | GITHUB | PORTFOLIO

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a foundation in marketing and finance, I bring over 6 years of professional leadership and collaborative experience to the role of a Full Stack Web Developer. Currently pursuing certification through Vanderbilt University's Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp, I am an intuitive problem-solver with a passion for creating apps that prioritize mobile-first design and development. My strengths lie in creativity, effective team collaboration, and successful project execution.

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development - Vanderbilt University | Nashville, TN|

Bachelor of Science, Marketing - Montana State University | Bozeman, MT|

Bachelor of Science, Marketing - University of Exeter |Exeter,UK|

TECHNICAL SKILLS

	7	
*	121/200	rint
	Javaso	.i ibt

Git

React.is

❖ jQuery

- MySQL
- Sequelize
- Express.js
- ❖ Node.js

- ❖ MongoDB
- ❖ NoSQL
- ❖ GraphQL
- ❖ MERN Stack

PROJECTS

PawFit| GitHub Repository | Deployment Link

- Summary: I am proficient in developing a full-stack application tailored for comprehensive pet health and data record management. The application allows users to effortlessly add pets, input relevant data, and securely store the information for future reference.
- Role: My responsibilities include creating and designing the database, implementing handlebars functionality, and ensuring a seamless user experience.
- Technology: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars, and Sequelize to build a robust and user-friendly platform for managing pet health records.

The Local List | GitHub Repository | Deployment Link

- Summary: Proficient in crafting a dynamic dashboard that showcases a 5-day weather forecast and real-time events for a user-specified city. I specialize in designing intuitive interfaces, implementing API functionality, and applying JavaScript logic for seamless user interactions.
- Role: I take charge of the design aspects, develop API functionality to fetch weather and event data, and implement robust JavaScript logic to ensure the dashboard's responsiveness and functionality.
- Technology: utilizing API integration, CSS for styling, and leveraging JavaScript and HTML to create an engaging and informative dashboard for users.

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS FINANCE MANAGER

JESCO MARINE & POWER SPORTS | Kalispell, MT | OCT 2022 - JULY 2023

- Assist in strategic decision making to manage 5-10 million in inventory, plan for brand growth, and forecast supply and demand
- Collaborate on marketing strategies, KPI's, campaigns, and event planning to align with business goals.
- Finalize on all contracts to ensure gross profit target of 15-25% is achieved
- Optimize CRM to identify the best fit in the marketing funnel during customer journey

RELATIONSHIP DEVELOPMENT & SUPPORT

BMO HARRIS BANK | Milwaukee, WI | MAR 2019- JUNE 2022

- Administered business relationships for internal and external divisions to foster new and current relationships
- Individually managed, tracked, and maintained 200+ customer accounts focusing on cost saving strategies to increase bottom line
- Led, trained, and managed the missing collateral department to identify and recover missing data for new and current contracts.
- Consistently hit monthly metrics, 95% efficiency, 100% work quality, and customer satisfaction.

EXPERT COACH/BRAND AMBASSADOR

SOLIDCORE |Milwaukee, WI| DEC 2020 - JUNE 2022

- Cultivated brand awareness in a competitive Pilates market by leveraging social channels, developing customer and business relationships.
- Built personal brand as professional, educated, and welcoming expert coach through both digital and in-person platforms.
- Collaborated with the team to grow a new studio into a top 5 revenue performer in the nation.
- Positioned myself as a specialized pro coach with innovative programming, knowledge in specialty classes, and priority in customer experience.